pspgweber.com 2014-06-29

# Privacy Policy and Terms of Service | PSPgweber

**Privacy Statement**

* * *

PSPgweber.com is committed to protecting your privacy. PSPgweber.com does not sell, trade or rent your personal information to other companies. PSPgweber.com will not collect any personal information about you except when you specifically and knowingly provide such information. The following contains details on how we treat all information collected on PSPgweber.com. 

**Log Files**

* * *

Like most standard Web site servers, I use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

**Third-party Advertisers, Links to Other Sites**

* * *

PSPgweber.com allows other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements within PSPgweber.com. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on PSPgweber.com. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content you see. PSPgweber.com does not provide any personally identifiable information to third-party ad servers or ad networks without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). 

**Cookies**

* * *

Cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. However, I have no access to or control over these cookies, once I have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising. You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts. Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added. 

**Intellectual Property Rights / Legal Agreement**

* * *

Contents on PSPgweber.com site submitted or posted by users, is provided to you for your personal use only and may not be used, copied, reproduced, distributed, transmitted, broadcast, displayed, sold, licensed, or otherwise exploited for any other purposes whatsoever without the prior written consent of the respective owners. PSPgweber.com does not store any copyright files on this server. Please contact us at PSPgweber AT gmail.com or the 3rd Party Hoster to report an abuse. We will removed the contents in 48-72 hours after we received the notice.
